(7:30 in the night)
(Ooh)
(I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, you come around, yeah)
(You ease my mind, you make everything feel fine)
(Worried 'bout those comments, I'm way too numb, yeah)
(It's way too dumb, yeah)
I get those goosebumps every time
I need that high, yeah
Throw that to the side, yeah
I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, when you're not around
When you throw that to the side, yeah
7-1-3 to the 281, yeah, I'm riding
While they on me, yeah
While they on me, I'm flying
Sipping low-key
I'm sipping low-key and honest
Swerving, riding
When I pull up right beside you
Pop star, Lil' Mariah
When I text, she get game wireless
Throw a stack on the Bible
Never slack 'til it took Molly
She fall through plenty, hurr' on all her guinness, yeah
We at the top floor, right there off do Henny, yeah
Oh, nah, oh, I can't fuck with y'all
Yeah, when I'm with my squad, I cannot do no wrong
Yeah, sauces in the city, don't get missing fawn
Yeah, they gon' pull up on you, brrr, brrr, brrr
Yeah, we gon' do some things, some things you can't relate
Yeah, 'cause we from a place, a place you cannot say
Or you can't go
Or I don't know
Or back the fuck up off me, yeah
(I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, you come around, yeah)
(You ease my mind, you make everything feel fine)
(Worried 'bout those comments, I'm way too numb, yeah)
(It's way too dumb, yeah)
I get those goosebumps every time
I need that high, yeah
Throw that to the side, yeah
I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, when you're not around
When you throw that to the side, yeah
I ain't wanna press my line, yeah
I ain't wanna green light, I wanna be light, I wanna press my line, yeah
I ain't wanna take that ride, yeah
I'm gonna press my line, yeah
I ain't wanna green light, I wanna be light, I wanna press my
Mama dear, spare your feelings, I'm relentless
Moments building more residual
I could buy the building, burn the building
Take your bitch, rebuild the building, just to fuck some more
I can justify my love for ya
I ain't touch the sky for us
Got a stop debating wall
Put the pussy on a pedestal
Put the pussy on a high horse
That pussy do die for
He'd pipe a pepper, pick the peppers
I could pick your brain and put your heart together
We'd depart the shady parts
We'd party hard through diamond showers that accrue forever
My best shots might shoot forever like...
I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, you come around, yeah
You ease my mind, you make everything feel fine
Worried 'bout those comments, I'm way too numb, yeah
It's way too dumb, yeah
I get those goosebumps every time
I need that high, yeah
Throw that to the side, yeah
I get those goosebumps every time, yeah, when you're not around
When you throw that to the side, yeah
I get those goosebumps every time, yeah